Contact

+923352995580 (Mobile) asadrasoolard@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/asadrasoolard (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

ASP.NET MVC

C#

JavaScript

Languages

English (Professional Working)

Certifications

Building React and ASP.NET MVC 5 Applications

Node.js for C# Developers

Blazor: Getting Started

React: Building Large Apps

.NET Essentials: Working with LINQ

Asad Rasool

Software Engineer | .Net Developer | ASP.Net MVC | JavaScript | C# | SQL | SAP B-One Integration |

Pakistan

Summary

My experience appears to be concentrated in Information Technology / Programming, with exposure to Purchasing, Procurement, Inventory Control, Supply Chain / Logistics. My experience appears to be ENTRY LEVEL, with 2 years of experience, with no management experience.

Experience

Dow University of Health Sciences Software Engineer April 2021 - Present (10 months) Karāchi, Sindh, Pakistan

Abacus Consulting

Research Associate

February 2020 - April 2021 (1 year 3 months)

Karachi

Working on the Software Development with the integration of SAP. Developing Web & Desktop App using the technology of ASP.Net MVC, C# .Net, Ajax, Json, JavaScript, JQuery & MSSQL and Hardware Integration of Weigh-bridge & PLC.

Star Denim Pvt Ltd
.NET Developer
July 2019 - November 2019 (5 months)
Karachi

Working on C# .Net Windows Form Application Crystals Reports for many invoices and track records and db MSSQL Server. I am handling existing ERP for making changes and error's remove and create the customise ERP for inhouse development.

EDP Services (Pvt.) Ltd. .NET Developer

April 2019 - July 2019 (4 months)

Karachi

Self-employed Freelance Developer January 2018 - February 2019 (1 year 2 months)

Education

Iqra University (Official)

Bachelors of Computer Science (BS), Computer Science · (2015 - 2018)